<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Simple Keto Journey - Journal</title><link href="https://simpleketojourney.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://simpleketojourney.com/feeds/journal.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://simpleketojourney.com/</id><updated>2021-11-18T16:01:06-06:00</updated><entry><title>Introductions are in order, I think</title><link href="https://simpleketojourney.com/posts/2021/11/18/introductions-are-in-order-i-think/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-11-18T16:01:06-06:00</published><updated>2021-11-18T16:01:06-06:00</updated><author><name>Shane</name></author><id>tag:simpleketojourney.com,2021-11-18:/posts/2021/11/18/introductions-are-in-order-i-think/</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Welcome to my world&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I know - you've been here before, just like me. What makes us think that this time is going to be any different?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't know the answer to that, either, but I do hope that we can all learn something here - about ourselves and about …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Welcome to my world&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I know - you've been here before, just like me. What makes us think that this time is going to be any different?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't know the answer to that, either, but I do hope that we can all learn something here - about ourselves and about wanting to be better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Historically, I've attempted to write before (I'm not going to call it a blog, because I can't say that I have ever been a fan of that word) in a journal style site such as this - fine, it's a blog. But I've not generally been all that successful. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The issue has been that my interests are so varied, however, I plan on using this site for a little more focused subject. Of which, in case one could not tell by the name of this site, is focused my Keto Journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;One fateful decision&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August 8, 2019. In two days I would be celbrating my 42nd birthday. I'd make a nice, chewy, chocolatey, ginormously thick brownie, cover that in some vanilla ice cream and devour who knows how much of it. Not a problem for a big 6 foot 2 inch tall guy who tipped the scales at 333 pounds plus. That was the day, however, that both my wife and I decided that we were done being obese and were ready to make some lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had talked about going keto for probably a decade - well, well before it was "the thing" that everybody did. Well, not everybody I'm sure, but before it was quite the popular option that it is now. We always had concerns though:
* "But it's going to be so expensive!" - well, sure it's going to be expensive to replace everything that we eat, and all that meat is gonna cost us...but, what about our health? Healthcare ain't cheap either!
* "But what if I fail?" - then you try again! Everybody has a fear of failure, and this was certainly one of mine.
* "But....carbs are my favorite food group!" - there is absolutely no doubt that giving up carbs, or going down to 20 or fewer carbs a day can be a challenge, it's certainly been a fun one to accomplish.
* I'm sure there are others, but we'll get to those in due time I'm sure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are definitely plenty of excuses for &lt;em&gt;Not&lt;/em&gt; doing keto. But that's all they are, excuses...&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Journal"></category></entry></feed>