<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Simple Keto Journey - Journal</title><link href="https://simpleketojourney.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://simpleketojourney.com/feeds/journal.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://simpleketojourney.com/</id><updated>2021-11-18T15:46:56-06:00</updated><entry><title>Intruductions are in order, I think</title><link href="https://simpleketojourney.com/posts/2021/11/18/intruductions-are-in-order-i-think/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-11-18T15:46:56-06:00</published><updated>2021-11-18T15:46:56-06:00</updated><author><name>Shane</name></author><id>tag:simpleketojourney.com,2021-11-18:/posts/2021/11/18/intruductions-are-in-order-i-think/</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Welcome to my world&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I know - you've been here before, just like me. What makes us think that this time is going to be any different?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't know the answer to that, either, but I do hope that we can all learn something here - about ourselves and about …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Welcome to my world&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I know - you've been here before, just like me. What makes us think that this time is going to be any different?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't know the answer to that, either, but I do hope that we can all learn something here - about ourselves and about wanting to be better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Historically, I've attempted to write before (I'm not going to call it a blog, because I can't say that I have ever been a fan of that word) in a journal style site such as this - fine, it's a blog. But I've not generally been all that successful. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The issue has been that my interests are so varied, however, I plan on using this site for a little more focused subject. Of which, in case one could not tell by the name of this site, is focused my Keto Journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;One fateful decision&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August 8, 2019. In two days I would be celbrating my 42nd birthday. I'd make a nice, chewy, chocolatey, ginormously thick brownie, cover that in some vanilla ice cream and devour who knows how much of it. Not a problem for a big 6 foot 2 inch tall guy who tipped the scales at 333 pounds plus. ...to be continued.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Journal"></category></entry></feed>